{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4868","name":"D C's Alabama Style Chicken Fish & Ribs","address":"15401 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48224","owner":"Damon Clark","licenseNumber":"077564","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","coords":"-82.94254,42.38844","geojson":{"id":"4868","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-82.9425385769999,42.3884411290001]},"properties":{"name":"D C's Alabama Style Chicken Fish & Ribs","owner":"Damon Clark","address":"15401 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48224","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"077564","establishmentid":"4868","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"365.0","most_recent_license_date":"5/3/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"5150","name":"Memories","address":"15421 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51622760","name":"Lost River","address":"15421 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51622630","name":"Veggininies Paradise Cafe","address":"15439 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"2002","name":"East Bar-Detroit","address":"15045 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"5408","name":"The French Cow (Crepes Shop)","address":"1349 Beaconsfield Ave","zipcode":"4823"},{"establishmentid":"1684","name":"Ye Olde Tap Room","address":"14915 Charlevoix","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"846","name":"Clark Elementary School","address":"15755 Bremen Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"5381","name":"Mack Coney Island","address":"14845 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"51622848","name":"Foodelicious","address":"14845 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"4126","name":"My Dad's Bar","address":"14911 Kercheval Ave","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"3332","name":"Chicken Shack","address":"14630 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"51622812","name":"Rich Man Poor Man","address":"14619 Kercheval Ave","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"2676","name":"Texas Bar and Grill","address":"14619 Kercheval","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"3768","name":"Krazy Pizza","address":"14300 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"3260","name":"St. John's Congregational Church","address":"14320 Kercheval Ave","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"2317","name":"Detroit Merit Academy","address":"1091 Alter Rd","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"2861","name":"Jeanie's Lounge","address":"16200 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"5250","name":"Warren Fresh Fish","address":"14900 E Warren","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"282","name":"Marshalls Bar","address":"14716 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"5406","name":"Norma G's Detroit","address":"14628 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48215"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"42431","inspectionDate":"2018-06-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FRYER AREA","subLocation":"Missing Light Shield(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide adequate light shields and end caps or shatter-proof bulbs."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Greasy","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Cookline","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"3-501.13","violationDescription":"POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be thawed:  Under refrigeration, or under cool running water (<70° F), or as part of cooking process, and total accumulated time above 41° F, for thawed portions, shall not exceed 4 hours.  Any thawing procedure may be used for immediate service for individual consumers order of READY-TO-EAT foods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Frozen food(s) for thawing","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored in water","subProblem":"That is standing","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Prep sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Use cool, running water with enough flow to remove particles."}]},{"inspectionid":"38624","inspectionDate":"2017-05-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-202.13","violationDescription":"An air gap between the water supply inlet and the flood level rim of the PLUMBING FIXTURE, EQUIPMENT, or nonFOOD EQUIPMENT shall be at least twice the diameter of the water supply inlet and may not be less than 1 inch. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Air gap","subItem":"between supply line and flood rim of plumbing fixture","problemDescription":"Less than twice the diameter of supply line","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Over head spray unit ","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide air gap that is twice the diameter of the drain line and no less than 1 inch."},{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"Raw ready-to-eat food(s) Vegetable(s)","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"In the Cooler (3  door)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"probe","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"No Product stem thermometer(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"Floor(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Cracked","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored with food-contact portion exposed","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE AREA(S)","subLocation":"On the Storage rack(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store inverted."},{"violationCode":"4-204.11","violationDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood systems in FOOD preparation and WAREWASHING areas including components such as hoods, fans, guards, and ducting shall be designed to prevent grease or condensation from draining or dripping onto FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Exhaust ventilation hood system(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Designed to allow grease or condensation from draining/dripping onto","subProblem":"Equipment","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Missing Grease collection device","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to prevent grease accumulation/dripping/draining."}]},{"inspectionid":"36104","inspectionDate":"2016-08-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4868"}}